Before we leave off, let's quickly go over
在继续学习之前
the different Amazon web services resources that we've
先快速浏览下我们使用过的不同 AWS 资源
used and make sure that everything has been shut down and cleaned out.
检查是否已关闭和清理一切
To begin with, you should make sure that any notebook that you have is stopped,
首先 必须停止所有的 notebook
that is not in service remember that you
不能处于服务状态
are charged for the length of time that your notebook instance is running.
因为 notebook 实例按照运行时长计费
So, if you have any running you should make sure to stop them.
如果有任何正在运行的实例 请停止
Also, you should double-check that you don't have any endpoints running.
此外 需要检查是否有任何端点在运行
Remember just like notebook instances,
与 notebook 实例一样
you are charged for the length of time that an endpoint is running for.
端点也按照运行时长计费
So if you have any running you should make sure to shut them down too.
如果有任何正在运行的端点 请关闭
Those are the sage maker specific resources that we've used throughout.
这些是我们一直使用的 SageMaker 资源
But let's take a look at some of the other Amazon services that we've used.
下面看看其他使用过的 Amazon 服务
Clicking on the top left corner,
点击左上角的 AWS 图标
we can go back to the main Amazon console.
回到主 Amazon 控制台
Aside from Sage Maker,
除了 SageMaker 之外
we've used three other Amazon Web Services.
我们还使用了其他三个 AWS 服务
The first is S3 which is listed here under storage.
第一个是 S3 列在了“Storage”下方
In the free tier, you're given a certain amount of storage and S3 that you
对于免费套餐 S3 上有一些存储空间
aren't charged for but beyond that or if you are no longer in free tier,
不需要付费 但是超出免费套餐之后
it costs you some small amount of money for the space that you occupy on S3.
就需要支付一小笔费用
So if you're done with all of the data you should make sure to delete it.
所以 如果使用完所有的数据 请删掉
In my case, I would just delete the entire bucket.
我直接删除整个存储桶
Heading back to the main console,
回到主控制台
one of the other services that we used was Amazon Lambda,
我们还使用了另一个服务是 Amazon Lambda
which is listed under the compute heading.
它列在了“Compute”下方
With Lambda, you're only charged whenever your Lambda function is executed,
Lambda 仅按照 Lambda 函数的执行次数计费
and in the free tier you're allowed to have
在免费套餐中
some number of executions before you're charged.
你可以免费执行一定的次数
If you don't want to have a Lambda function hanging around in your account,
如果不想在帐号中保留 Lambda 函数
you can just make sure delete it.
请删掉它
I've already deleted mine.
我已经删了我的 Lambda 函数
Lastly, heading back to the main console,
最后 回到主控制台
the third Amazon service that we used was API gateway.
我们使用的第三个 Amazon 服务是 API Gateway
You can get to API Gateway by scrolling down to networking and content delivery.
向下一直滚动到“Networking &amp; Content Delivery”部分就能找到 API Gateway
Remember that API Gateway allowed us to create
API Gateway 使我们能够
an endpoint that sent data to the Lambda function.
创建一个向 Lambda 函数发送数据的端点
If you don't want any endpoint configurations hanging around on your account,
如果你不希望帐号中保留任何端点配置
you can also delete that here.
也可以在这里删掉它
I've already done that.
我已经删了
That's it for the Amazon services that we used in this module.
这些就是我们在此模块中使用的 Amazon 服务
It's a good idea to make a habit of going through and checking each of the resources
建议养成良好习惯 定期检查你使用过的资源
that you've used to make sure you don't have anything
看看是否有任何资源还在运行
hanging around that may incur a cost.
并产生费用